var quizData = [{
        "question": "What year was the first Iron Man movie released, kicking off the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
        "answer": "2008"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Avenger does Thor team up with in Thor: Ragnarok?",
        "answer": "hulk"
    }, {
        "question": "In which fictional country is Black Panther set?",
        "answer": "wakanda"
    }, {
        "question": "In which film did Hawkeye first appear?",
        "answer": "thor"
    }, {
        "question": "Who kills Thanos?",
        "answer": "ironman"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Ironman movie sequels are there at present?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who besides Thor lifts his hammer in End Game?",
        "answer": "captain america"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many infinity stones are there?",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Thor's new weapon called??",
        "answer": "stormbreaker"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who besides Thor lifts his hammer in End Game?",
        "answer": "captain america"
    },
]